Hey guys.
We're here today learning how to play some fun new improv warm-ups for your improv team, and the next warm-up that Dan B. and I are going to show you is a warm-up called Robot.
Now to play Robot, you're going to have your team partner up into pairs of two.
Each pair is then going to take turns getting up on stage.
One person is going to stand right there on the front of the stage and the other person is either going to be off to the side of the stage or down below so that he's off stage or off frame.
The person, actor who is down below is going to make a bunch of crazy noises that they think a robot would make, and the player that's on stage has to physically move and justify the noises that are being made.
The crazier and the more off the wall you can get with your noises, the more fun and the more challenging it's going to be for the actor that is on stage.
So for this example I think Dan is going to make some noises, and I'm going to try to justify them with my body language as a robot would.
Alright.
I'm going to start off with a blank slate.
(Beeps, robot noise.)
And that's how you play Robot.